Live for one night only... that's all they ever need.
Black Roses is a horror, music film directed by John Fasano.
Teens in a small conservative town are turned into evil demons
thanks to the music of the titular heavy metal band.
Matthew Moorhouse, played by John Martin.
Mayor Farnsworth, played by Ken Swofford.
Vinny Apache, played by Carmine Appice.
Mrs. Miller, played by Julie Adams.
Damian, played by Sal Viviano.
Johnny Pratt / Demon Guitarist, played by Frank Dietz.
Black Roses is a 1988 horror film directed by John Fasano and starring
John Martin, Ken Swofford, Julie Adams, and Carla Ferrigno.
The film's soundtrack features many bands of the era, including King
Kobra, Tempest, Hallow's Eve and Lizzy Borden, among others.
Most of the music for the band Black Roses was performed by the members of King
Kobra, with Marcie Free on vocals and Carmine Appice on drums.
The tone is dark.